Friends, in this video, I will compare
health insurance companies,
what are their features, and how can you select a
health insurance company online
without wasting time like
people do. But friends,
in this video, I will compare health
insurance companies.
If you want to compare health insurance, there are many
website platforms in the market today.
You can compare health insurance and
try to make the best decision.
But I am a good web aggregator
which is popular nowadays, like Policy Bazaar.
On their website, how can you
compare policies?
Well,
we do health insurance. After that, in the next video,
I will also make a comparison of term insurance.
How do you compare and
what are the features? How can
you select a health insurance company online?
Where to get the right policy
depends on you.
But there is a comparison platform, so let's do it. Let's
start the video, let's not discuss,
we just talk about the issue. Okay,
we
After coming to the Policy Bazaar website, we see
health insurance, okay this is health insurance,
we have to select health insurance
here, I had
checked something previously, I had done some
comparison, so friends, as soon as
we selected health insurance,
your option is coming here, male, female, self is coming, self is
coming, okay,
wife, okay, we ticked the wife's option, okay,
and here the son has become one,
one daughter, okay, we compare the Ps,
okay, more members, if you want more
members, you can add father
here, if you want to add father, you can add father, if you want to add mother, you
can add mother, if you add more members, then
your premium will come according to that,
but here we calculate the husband, wife and two children,
okay, let's go to continue, so
friends, if we talk about the
age of the wife, we have kept the age of the husband as 38 years
Age is 40 years and one son is 8
years old, one is 4 years old and one is 4 years old daughter, okay let's
continue further, here
I have kept the option of Delhi, if
you want then
you can keep the option of any city, continue further, for example, if
I have any old number, I have entered my old
number in it so that I am
not disturbed by calls, otherwise
you may get a lot of calls, if you
give your personal regular number then you will be
very disturbed, if
you have to enter some medical history here, like
suppose if you have diabetes then
tick in diabetes, if you have heart disease then tick in heart, if you have
blood pressure then
tick in blood pressure, right,
what is there here, if you have any surgery, previous
medical history, any surgery, asthma,
okay, then if you have any problem, any trouble, it is
very important for you to tell that, it is a
material fact, basically all these are the material
facts, like if you have diabetes
or medical history, heart disease,
thyroid, any other, if you have any disease, then
any  If you have any disease, then it is
important for you to tell that too. If you do not have any of these things,
okay, if there is nothing, then
you have to tick none of this here, that means you do
not have any disease or any previous medical history, okay, so here
you have ticked none of this,
as soon as it comes here, does your office
provide you with health insurance, if
someone is asking about your corporate coverage, whether you have any
policy from the
company, then
I will mark no here,
okay, if yes, then you can say yes, it does
not make any difference, there is no problem like this,
if suppose you
also have a corporate policy, you have a policy from the company, from here
also you have taken a claim individually by taking a policy,
if suppose you
took 10 lakh from the corporate, 10 lakh from here, then you can claim from anyone,
as soon as 10 lakh expires, then
you can take a claim from both,
right, so first you will have to finish one,
after that you can take the other  You can start it, that is, you
can take someone else's claim. This is how we
go about it in OO plans. As soon as we
click on OO plan, we click on OO plans.
Now let's see, let's proceed further. So,
we have many options which are going to come now. Many
companies which have tie-ups with Policy Bazaar are very big companies.
If you want to customize, there is an
option on this, see, there is an option of month on this, okay, but the option
of month is coming, the
option of only is coming. Now see here, you have
options, you can see a little, let me see on this, so
friends, you see, on this, the
plan of Ker Supreme is coming, okay, the
plan of Ker is coming, the premium of 10 lakh,
if we see, it is coming 3658. The premium
of NIB is Brij Plus Val Direct Plan, in which
your premium is coming 16000 only,
okay, the superstar of 10 lakh,
how much is coming,
18600. And here your Active One Combo
in which 2 is coming, Aditya  Damn
ADFC ER is coming for 27000 okay this is the
elevated plan here, this is the load, it is
18000 154 now the cheapest one will be
shown at the top okay if the
cheapest one is shown then what will you do, what will you do, the one
which is cheaper is the best
okay there must be some reason behind the cheap plan or there is a
plan of 2000, a plan of 27000 and
you are getting a plan for how much is it,
you should think about this plan you should have taken health
insurance brother, is the TV or mobile freezing, you turned
on the TV after seeing the TV feature and
your picture is on but health insurance does
not have such a system
what will you get health insurance, it will have huge
pages, small letters which you will
never read, it is of 60-70 pages, you will
keep it without reading but it has
terms and conditions i.e. terms and conditions,
if you go round to the hospital then you will come to know that
this is not a cover, you paid 13000, it
seems that the bill there was for 3 lakhs  And if you do
n't have lakhs, right? So this is the thing
for that. There is some capping etc. here.
Look here, the biggest thing I am showing
you is that you should see this thing.
Like you are seeing it cheap, see
what is written on it. You will take the
policy, you will purchase it. Okay, here it is being said that
in Ker Supreme, it is giving you
20% copayment for treatment outside the
network list. If you
go outside the network list, then brother, how much copayment will be charged.
20% copayment.
20% copayment. If you go outside the network list,
as soon as your bill comes, you will get lakhs.
Plus, if there are 10 lakhs in it, that too, if it is a
single private room, then
you have a cap here. Okay, unlimited ration
cover is there. 5 lakhs bonus. Okay, so these are the
biggest features which are the copayment option.
As soon as the payment comes, your premium is settled.
Okay, it is
very important to see the copayment that there is no copayment in your policy.  There will be a
hidden factor, that is why the
premium is cheap, that is why it is
very important for you to see these facts, okay, now
here you will come in the view features, you
can go here and check the features of the company, what
are the features, view all features, okay,
now as if you tick on features, then
basically if you see,
you can check the features here,
clean paid within three months is written,
100% room rent, as I told you, in single
private room, there is capping here in room rent,
as soon as you go from single private room to
any category of rented room, it is
not just the room rent, here all your other
charges, all the
charges like nursing, doctor
consultation, diagnosis, that is,
all your charges become high,
so there is capping here, that is why
its premium is low, after that the biggest
thing is the comment, okay, so
because of the comment, its premium is cheap, so it is
very important for you to see that whichever health
insurance you choose, do not
look for the cheapest, okay, so in this  If it is in this way then you
are here now you have to do the comparison,
okay now there is another plan, if
you want to do the comparison, right, then
if you want to do the comparison then here you have to compare,
okay,
in this we pressed click, so look here one,
Rish Braj has come below
and we have taken one more plan of
Star Health, okay one more plan
i.e. we can compare three plans,
like suppose we have taken Active One
Como of Aditya Bala, we have compared this, okay, then we will compare all
three,
your Compare Now option will come here below, as soon as
you press Compare Now, you will get the
option, see here there
is an option like Rish Braj Plus,
Value Direct has become Superstar,
Active One Como has become, so here
you can see all the three plans, like it
is showing here, Room Rent, in this there is a single private
room, here you can take a room of any category,
in each other there is a single private room,
so in this way it is  You
can see in the comparison how much renewal bonus you will
get in it, okay, after that your single
private room, any category, all these
things, there is a co-payment option here,
so the comparison
is showing all these things here, so in this way you
can also compare a plan,
okay, you have already seen the premium, so
I just want to
conclude this video, if you want to do it then this is the best
option for you, right, so do a comparison
and you can buy the best plan for you by comparing it
from the market, but
you are facing a lot of issues in comparing, you are
facing problems, you can contact our team, the
number is given above, you can call on the number, our team will
help you in purchasing the best from the health insurance market,
we have almost more than 15 years of experience in the market,
we have settled claims of many people
in Osment, we have also
settled a lot of claims from Osment, clients who are
not company claims  She wanted to give, we got that
claim which was a genuine claim. See, if there is
any such claim which is fake or a
false claim, then we never support it.
If it is a claim of a genuine customer, then the
company has to give the claim to the customer, so for that
we take action and
we support the customer. If any of your claims
is stuck or there is any issue in such a genuine claim, then only
you can contact us. Our
team will help you in getting the claim. Plus,
if you want to purchase a new policy, then
we will provide you the best option.
After that claim, you will
purchase the policy from somewhere,
but the claim service is very important,
so our team is completely dedicated to
providing claim service. So,
if you purchase a policy from our side, then
you can get very good help in the claim.
If you are an NRI,
like you are an Indian origin NRI, then
even if you come to India,
you have to purchase the policy.  You can contact us on an all-
India basis. Plus,
if you are abroad, we
can still issue a policy for you. If you are an NRI, then
contact us. If you are
not working in health insurance, you are a life
insurance agent, or a mutual fund
distributor, you are making a big mistake.
You should provide health insurance to your clients
so that
in the future, at least in case of a medical emergency,
their savings, their
capital, their property, their jewellery, at least
they are not exhausted, at
least they do not have to spend money. If a
mediclaim claim comes, right? That is why
you should immediately hire a health insurance agency.
If you want to buy a health insurance agency, then this is a
great opportunity for you.
You are getting a chance to connect with an experienced person.
Join us.
In the coming time, you will get excellent
support. The
nearest branch will be provided to you in the city where you are located.
We are recruiting agency agents for Nibha Bappa Health Insurance.
And plus, for Tata AIG
General Insurance, we  We recruit agents on
all India level basis,
our service is available, you can contact us
for an agency, if you like the rest of the video, please
share it with your family, your friends, relatives, do give a like to the video
because it takes a
lot of hard work to make a video, so if you
like it, we will get motivation to make
another great video in the coming time,
right, on which
topic should I make the next video, please comment so that in the
next video I can bring you the best
video and give you the best knowledge of health
insurance and financial market, till then
bye bye, take care of yourself, we will meet
in the next video with a new content, till then
Jai Hind Vande Mataram